[Music] It has happened
[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to Option Gyan channel,
friends, by taking the opposite stock
limit, whose name is
V-guard, you have to buy this stock at the current
rate, that is, you have to back it around 263
and if it goes down, friends, then you have to
wish for 24 introduction,
I will send you 24 first, the next one will be more
spicy, friends, it will be around 229,
now if the
stock goes below 220 and
stays below 220 for a day or two, then you will get ready for your
position, friends, the market is at
its lifetime level, so in
such a situation, you should invest your equal 50% capital
in the market, whatever correction comes in the market,
we will interact with the full episode,
but do not
stop investing, friends, if you do not invest, then
you will not know
when there is a decline in the market, that this stock has to be bought
and in which stock, now see the positive close,
so you people stay in the market, even if the
market goes up, you will
get the benefit and if it goes down  So you will have
50% capital friends, you have to invest only 30% capital in this stock at the
current trend of 263, that is,
you have to
invest 40% of your capital at 24
and around October 29, the
remaining 30% has to be invested. So,
you should not always be a bull in every stock,
you should always assume that if you give up, then
my profit will be up
and it will go down, so I will calculate it here,
so you should have both the things, if it goes to 24, I will
book profit, if it goes
down, I will calculate 24 and below which price the
chart will become negative, then if it
remains below that, then I will select the stock,
friends, sometimes you will definitely regret
that I edited and where did the stock
turn from, but do not regret it
because if ever a case like Yes Bank or
IVRCL Infra happens, then you
people will see the highest profit that you people have made, so that is why you should
never get married to the stock,
see that whatever our level is, is it up to that
level, then it is okay, if the level is broken,
friends, exit  Get out and when it becomes positive again, either
you guys re-enter,
you will definitely make a profit if you follow any rule,
you will make a profit. Secondly,
friends, you guys feel that if we
buy a stock, it will be lost at that very moment. This does not happen.
Give time to the market. If you get an
FD done, then you get 516 bus stops in that too. Friends, if you do
any work, friends, you
give time to it, then you
should not hurry in the stock market that I start making
money today from AIO state.
Friends, if you want to
earn money on Friday, then for this we will have to acquire a lot of
knowledge and
learn a lot in the market or we will have to take
training from somewhere. It is a very long
step in anything, friends, you guys
take time. To become a doctor, you guys
take an MBBS degree. If
you do any professional work, then you will have to
take a degree. Why do we feel in the stock market that
if we come, then
money will start getting printed from tomorrow? So
understand this, if you work in a proper way, then there will
definitely be a benefit. This is my own
thinking.  You can do it the way you like.
Whatever video I am making, I make it
for your location purpose
so that you can also understand where to back,
how to wish, how to book profit. If
you friends follow only one stock of
mine, then you will get a lot of
benefit because whatever stock I provide,
its fundamentals are very strong,
but still select at least four or
five stock gurus. Out of all the
stocks that I have provided, all the stocks are
good, if you share any four-five of them, then
you will start getting profit,
your portfolio will grow very quickly,
friends, although the market is live time, so in
such a situation, there can be a
correction in the market, once you have
equity in your portfolio, but
where I am asking you to press,
if you press here and then do it with the same speed, then
you will definitely
benefit in the long term, friends. Now, once we
discuss it fundamentally,
yes, it is definitely there, but friends, in this you will click on the stock,
then there was a fundamental
window here.  Going into the fundamentals, you have to go into the
details. This is the ticket, but it will
bring you the
great scientific end of the company. If we talk about the
company's financial trend,
you will see it increasing.
Friends, if you compare the
photo in 128 on one hand, then it has
almost increased its profit by 70%.
If we talk about the financial statements, then the
company's revenue growth,
friends, is more than the industry's revenue growth
medium. The company has now
increased its market share for 5 years and has
control over the net income point, then friends,
you will see something amazing. While the
industry's net interest margin
is 5.3 percent,
friends, the company's profit margin is 12.5%, which is
more than double the net income version.
Now you can understand why I am referring this stock to you.
You
can consider it for both positional and long term. Whenever it gets into a dip,
you can invest in it.  You can add
I hope you liked my video
and it will be very useful for you
I end my video with this hope
thank you
so friends if you like this video
please don't forget to like share and subscribe thank
you for watching my video
[Music]